{
    "subject": "resource/The_Mandarin_Mystery",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "The Mandarin Mystery",
    "human_readable": "The name of The Mandarin Mystery is The Mandarin Mystery.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.879352867603302,
            "question": "Is 'The Mandarin Mystery' a correct title for the book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8379170298576355,
            "question": "Who is the author of The Mandarin Mystery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7576183080673218,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of The Mandarin Mystery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7305623888969421,
            "question": "What genre is The Mandarin Mystery likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021405100822449,
            "question": "When was The Mandarin Mystery published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000920534133911,
            "question": "Where can I find a copy of The Mandarin Mystery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5507763624191284,
            "question": "Are there any other books by the same author as The Mandarin Mystery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5333970785140991,
            "question": "Has The Mandarin Mystery been adapted into a film or television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.056620653718709946,
            "question": "What is the name of the book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.010797231458127499,
            "question": "Does the book have any other titles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of The Mandarin Mystery is The Mandarin Mystery.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5241_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5241_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has The Mandarin Mystery been adapted into a film or television show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5241_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other books by the same author as The Mandarin Mystery?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5241_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5241_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all documents mention \"The Mandarin Mystery\" as the title of a movie, and none of them contradict this statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe query \"The name of The Mandarin Mystery is The Mandarin Mystery.\" is correct according to the documents provided, as all relevant text mentions the title as \"The Mandarin Mystery\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}